Get out of here! You can't make me give you the key!
And even if you did, I wouldn't show you how to use it!
What's going on? Are they fighting about something?
What should I do? It'd be rude to eavesdrop.
But if they are fighting, I should try to help, shouldn't I?
Stop it!
What are you doing? Let him go!
There's no need to be so noisy. Who are you?
How could you treat a kid like that? You should...
He's not even budging.
Even though he's got thinner arms and a smaller body than me.
You take your hands off of me.
You're weaker than I thought. I'm surprised you got into the core.
Huh?
That box... I can sense something's in it. A demon, perhaps?
What are you hiding in there? Show me.
Stay back!
Thank you.
You think I'm being cruel.
Really?
Yes, I do.
Even though most of what you said is probably right.
And you can't fight like a Hashira.
Swordsmiths are still vital.
And that's a fact.
They might not fight, but the skills they have are amazing.
Without them, we wouldn't have any swords.
It's thanks to them that we can fight.
It's true that they need us.
But it's also true that we need them.
We're all fighting the same battle here.
Day in and day out, each in our own way.
Apologies.
But I don't have time to waste on your speech.
You understand.
What do we do?
I don't know if I can carry him by myself.
No worries.
I'll carry him back.
As long as he doesn't wake soon.
His eyelids are twitching.
Which means he's gonna wake up any second.
See ya!
Hey!
Are you okay?
You shouldn't get up so fast.
Mr. Hageneska!
Huh?
Was he here just now?
No!
I mean, why would he be?
Really?
Thought I heard him.
The Hashira!
I ended up giving him the key so he took off.
So you gave it to him.
I guess you didn't have a choice.
Well, since I don't know what's going on, I shouldn't be making a fuss.
No, it's okay.
I'm happy.
You don't know me, but you stood up for me.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry I wasn't able to help much.
Wait, what happened to that man?
Where'd he go?
Oh, that was a mechanical doll.
Mechanical doll?
Yeah, and that guy took it away with him.
You see, he needed the key in order to make the doll move.
So that's why it was important.
But why does he want that doll?
Because it's very special.
Not only can that mechanical doll overpower a human,
but it's capable of 108 different moves.
It's often used for combat training.
So that's why.
But now it's...
What was that?
Don't tell me he's already... this way!
Against the Hashira. Amazing.
Isn't it?
It's the battle type mechanical doll built by my ancestors.
The Yorichi Type Zero.
But...
Why does he have six arms?
Oh, his arms?
I asked the same thing.
According to my father,
that mechanical doll was modeled after an actual swordsman.
And the only way they could manage to replicate the swordsman's moves
was by giving it six arms.
That face...
It seems familiar.
But why?
About that swordsman...
Who exactly was he?
Uh...
Sorry, but I don't really know much about him.
He was from the Sengoku period.
S...
Sengoku?
You mean he lived more than 300 years ago?
That's what I was told.
In all that time, it's never broken down?
Incredible.
The technology's so advanced,
we're still not able to catch up to it.
So if it were to break,
there'd be no fixing it.
My father suddenly passed away,
and I have no siblings.
I'm the only one who can step up now.
But I'm no good with swords or dolls.
So that's why you...
I think I get it now.
Wow.
He's incredible.
Even though we're around the same age.
He's talented.
And a Hashira.
Well, duh!
What did you expect?
I mean, he is a descendant of sun breathing users after all.
That boy is a prodigy, you know.
He's in a different league than the likes of you.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Are you Tokito's crow?
Wait, sun breathing?
The first breathing style?
So he really is that amazing.
But that isn't sun breathing, right?
If you don't quit your yapping,
I'm gonna catch your eyes out!
Hey, now I remember.
My dream.
Yeah, I saw that man in my dream.
Huh?
Are you an idiot or something?
Isn't this your first time here too?
You sure know how to make me laugh,
I'll give you that.
You met a warrior from the Sengoku period?
How old are you exactly?
Huh?
Listen, I'm sorry.
I...
I must be crazy.
No!
I know.
Maybe it's an inherited memory.
People talk about those a lot in our village.
It isn't just your physical form that gets passed on.
Living creatures pass on their memories too.
Huh?
So what you saw in your dream
had to have been your ancestors' memories!
That's preposterous!
Actually preposterous!
How kind of you.
Thank you.
Ha!
I'm Tanjiro.
What's your name?
My name's Kotetsu.
You can just do what I always do
and ignore the mean lady crows!
Hey!
His armor!
Kotetsu!
I'll find you!
I've got a good nose!
Even if it's a bit out of shape.
I think he ran off this way...
...
Kotetsu! Kotetsu! I'll find you! I've got a good nose!
Even if it's a bit out of shape. I think he ran off this way.
Kotetsu! How in the world did you manage to climb up that high?
Come on, you can't give up on your doll. I'll do anything I can to help you out.
What about your future?
If you try hard now for your future self, then a day will come where you can fight and stand up for yourself.
No, it won't. I'm smart enough to know that I'm a loser, okay? Because of me, it's all gonna end with my generation!
Huh? Ouchie!
You cannot give up and walk away from it. I really wish you wouldn't talk about yourself that way.
He didn't make a sound! Swordsmen are scary!
Even if you can't do it, there will be someone who will carry on for you. You have to do what you can so it gets passed on. If you fail, maybe your kids or grandkids will succeed.
I want to be the one to put an end to Muzan Kibutsu-chi. And to save my sister who's been turned into a demon. I might die before I fulfill my goals.
Huh?
But I have faith that someone will carry out my wishes, the same way we were able to when we beat an upper rank. So I know in my heart that someday, Muzan Kibutsu-chi will fall!
Let's give her all!
I… I couldn't stand to watch him break the door. But that was before! The combat training should last until nightfall. I promise I'll see this through! To the end!
Yeah! Really? So you're Tenko Tetsu?
Yeah! My little brother is… Huh? What? You're already done?
I'm finished. It made for good training. Do I know you? Oh, that's right. My sword snapped, so…
Huh?
This will do. For the time being.
Kotetsu!
There. Now dispose of it.
Not even a whiff of malice. He must not be doing it on purpose. That being said…
His crow is oozing with animosity. She's so condescending. What gives?
Oh! Kotetsu!
Kotetsu. Let's make sure. And see if it still works.
Uh…
Nothing… It must be…
Alright! It's working, Kotetsu! That's… great!
Yes it is, Mr. Tanjiro. And do you know why? Because now you can train with this doll and become stronger than that indifferent little jerk! And you'll have my full support, no matter what!
Huh? Wait, right now?
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
Whoaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
Wooooahhhhhh!
I'm gonna die! Six arms is so many!
There are only five arms! Since that lousy jerk broke one off, it's way easier to beat now!
It's way easier to beat now.
Mr. Tanjiro, please, we need you stronger.
So next time we see him, you can say,
That all you got, you scumbag?
It's time to get a haircut, seaweed head.
Piss here! Your ugly and your legs are short!
Commit seppuku, you shameless jerk!
No! Mr. Kotetsu! That's going too far!
You think we should put his head on public display?
What? No! I'm not saying any of that!
Yes, you are!
No!
Please say it! Please!
Tokito was incredible. He hardly broke a sweat.
Despite being smaller and younger than me,
I have to train harder so that I can become stronger.
Come on, Mr. Tanjiro! Don't tell me that's all it takes to kill you!
Now, come on! Get up! I'm gonna say it one more time! Look at me!
All you're doing now is moving out of habit, Mr. Tanjiro!
You're not reacting off your opponent's moves whatsoever!
That's why you're getting beat, understand?
Which in other words means you don't even have the fundamentals of sword fighting down yet!
It's a miracle you haven't died!
Good thing I'm here to expose your weak points until we fix them!
And to give you some extra motivation, no food until we're finished!
Right...
Faster, Mr. Tanjiro! You gotta pick up the pace!
If that doll wasn't armed with practice sticks, you'd be dead! Get it together!
We're on day five now, so starting tomorrow, I'm gonna arm the doll with swords!
That is... if I even live to see day six, I'm... I'm gonna die!
No food for you today, either!
Mr. Kotetsu's surprisingly analytical.
But as a swordsmanship instructor, he was terrible!
It's like he has no idea what the limits of the human body are.
And his brutal training reflects that.
He's gotten to be so ruthless, that he'll withhold food and water if you fall short.
But a human can only go without water for three days or so.
It's pure tyranny, born out of his ignorance.
Luckily, I was able to survive thanks to rainfall.
All throughout these harsh training sessions, I went without water, without food, without sleep.
And then, I started to cross the river to the afterlife.
I was walking across a bridge, feeling an indescribable bliss, only to get dizzy from hunger and fall in the river.
The water got darker and darker, heavier and heavier, until I felt a strange warmth.
It was almost like I was being massaged.
When I glanced towards the bottom of the river, I saw something shiny.
So I swam towards it while being massaged.
Oddly enough, despite being underwater, I could smell the shimmering stone.
What is this?
The smell?
It's different than the opening thread.
Left side of the head!
Neck!
Right side!
Left side!
Right thigh!
Right shoulder!
Now!
Left side!
There you go!
You finally got one strike in!
Though it was so weak, I don't think the doll even flinched.
Congrats!
You earned some food!
Rice balls and pickled plums!
And I want high-quality gyokuro tea!
Tasty!
Good!
His moves!
I see them!
I see them much better than before!
And I've got my stamina back now!
Somehow, I can tell by the scent where he's going to strike!
Even better!
I can pick up the scent faster than the opening thread!
Yes!
I can do it!
I can land a full-strength blow!
But what if it breaks?
Do it!
If it does break, then I... then I'll just fix it!
Mr. Tanjiro, you're far too kind!
But there's no time to hesitate!
If you do, it's sure to cost you your life!
And I don't want that!
What I want is for you to be the strongest!
That hurt!
Mr. Tanjiro!
Are you alright?
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Sorry!
I broke the sword that you lent me!
Don't worry about that!
It's okay!
Huh?
Hey!
Something came out!
C-C-Codetsu, something came out!
What is that?!
Don't ask me!
It's not like I put it in there!
Can I put it in there?!
What could that possibly be?!
It's a sword!
But it's gotta be at least 300 years old, right?
Right?
命が震えさわる
混沌 こんな時代に
恋に落ちて
悲しみが世界を何度打ち沸かしても
しなやかに舞う
君の居合い場が
夢が通る道を開く
愛し合って笑いたいな
優しい人たちを全部
守りたいな
届くんだ 望めばきっと
君の声が僕を呼んで
長く夢のような
朝焼けが空を焼く
昼へ 朝の向こうへ
走り出した美しい世界に
恋焦がれて
愛し合って笑う
愛し合って笑い
待ってる
専門家計を
提供させよう
適合に
歩くの
社交際に
escuchし
組め圖
コべてクイatur
流 stem
履 жив
移り
Mr. Tanjiro, where are you?
Nasuko, let's go!
Mr. Tanjiro, where are you hiding?
No!